Whether you love to belt out tunes at karaoke or just sing in the shower, it turns out that singing can be good for both physical and mental health.
不管你是喜欢在卡拉OK放声高歌，还是只爱在淋浴时哼上几句，事实证明，唱歌对身心健康都大有裨益。
And you don't even have to be good at it!
而且你甚至不需要唱得有多好听！
The physical and mental advantages of singing are caused by a combination of factors, according to Baishali Mukherjee from the World Federation of Music Therapy.
世界音乐治疗联合会的巴伊沙莉·慕克吉表示，唱歌带来的身心益处是多种因素共同作用的结果。
He told BBC Future, "The physical exertion involved in singing – filling of our lungs, the firm control of our vocal cords, the movements of our mouth and body – is among the reasons why it can boost our mood."
他在接受BBC未来频道采访时说：“唱歌时的身体活动——充盈肺部、稳定控制声带、嘴巴和身体的协调动作——都是它能改善我们心情的原因之一。”
Hitting all the notes involves breathing control and the use of the diaphragm. This can lead to an increase of oxygen intake and lung capacity.
唱准每一个音符需要控制呼吸并运用横膈膜，这会增加氧气摄入量，提升肺活量。
Also, apparently, singing in a group brings just as many benefits as singing solo.
并且，似乎合唱和独唱带来的益处不相上下。
It has been estimated that over 2.2 million people in Britain now regularly sing in a choir.
据估计，目前英国有超过220万人定期参加合唱团。
A choir can be amateur or professional and is made up of people who sing together, often in harmony with different people singing different parts, such as soprano or tenor, according to their vocal range.
合唱团分业余和专业两种，由在一起唱歌的人组成，成员会根据自身音域分唱不同声部，比如女高音或男高音，从而演绎出和声效果。
A 2022 University of Vienna study found that choral singing enhances feelings of trust and bonding among a group, which can help with depression and loneliness.
维也纳大学2022年的一项研究发现，合唱能增强群体成员之间的信任感和凝聚力，这有助于缓解抑郁和孤独感。
And, aside from mood-boosting, other proven mental health benefits of singing include a lowering of stress and anxiety levels due to the release of endorphins – the so-called "happy hormones".
除了改善心情之外，唱歌对心理健康的其他经证实的益处还包括：唱歌会促使分泌内啡肽——即所谓的“快乐荷尔蒙”，从而降低压力和焦虑水平。
So, whether you are a confident vocalist or not, give singing a go!
所以，无论对于唱歌是否自信，你都不妨试试！
You don't need an instrument because that's you.
你不需要任何乐器，因为你自己就是乐器。
And yes, you might forget the lyrics or sound a little out of tune, but remember, there are a wealth of positives.
没错，你可能会忘词，也可能会跑调，但请记住，唱歌带来的好处数不胜数。